http://www.personalisedbanners.co.uk/privacy.html

Shop MenuThis Is Your Life BannersBirthday BannersWelcome Home BannersWedding BannersChristening BannersMilitary BannersGood Luck BannersMiscellaneous BannersPostersUK delivery from just£2.95Various options available, incl. Saturday delivery and international shipping.Help & SupportContact UsDelivery InformationReturns & RefundsPrivacy PolicyTerms & ConditionsCustomer ReviewsBanner InformationHelp & FAQsBanner SizesPricing InformationPhoto EnquirySocial Media PolicyPrivacy PolicyYour privacy is important to usThis privacy policy sets out how Bannerama uses and protects any information that you give to Bannerama when you use this website. Bannerama is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.Bannerama may change this policy from time to time by updating this page.Cookies informationYou can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. Some cookies used on this website are essential in order to enable you to move around the website and use its features, such as accessing secure areas of the website. Without these cookies ordering personalised banners and posters cannot be completed.Some cookies used on this website collect information about how visitors use a website. For instance, which pages visitors go to most often, and if they get error messages from web pages. These cookies don't collect information that identifies a visitor. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. It is only used to improve how a website works.Some cookies used on this website allow the website to remember choices you make (such as your user name, language or the region you are in) and provide enhanced, more personal features. These cookies can also be used to remember changes you have made to text size, fonts and other parts of web pages that you can customise. The information these cookies collect may be anonymised and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites.Cookies may also be used to improve the user experience and to enable some of the functionality provided by this website.Please note: some cookies may be placed by third party service providers who perform some of these functions (or other services) for us. Cookies are used on this website by the following third party services: Google Analytics, Google +1 button, AddThis social bookmarking tool. Some of these services may be used to track your behaviour on other websites and we have no control over this.Your visit to our siteAs is true with most websites, our server will automatically log data regarding each visit such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system. We may use this information to monitor server errors, server administration or to monitor visitor behaviour. It is not possible for this to be disabled on a per-user basis so you must leave this website if you do not agree to this happening.Your photos and personal informationWe only use your photographs to create the banner or poster, shortly after printing the files you supplied and the file used to create the banner are deleted from our servers. We will never post your images or banner on any social media site, see our Social Media Policy. The images shown on the template banners have been sourced from Public Domain websites such as Pixabay and Pexels.If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. This privacy policy applies to this website only and does not apply to any websites that this website may link to. We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to any third parties, unless we are required by law to do so.If you have any questions or comments about this policy, you should contact us.Sign up for updates & offers *Enter your email address and hit 'submit' to be added to our mailing list and be kept informed of the latest news and special offers.SubmitSubmitKeep in touch!Our friendly sales team are ready and waiting to help, so get in touch right away if you need any help shopping with us or creating your perfect banner!Call us on: 01473 832851 (9.15am until 4.45pm, Monday to Friday)Email us directly at: sales@bannerama.co.ukSecure online payments
100% secure payments taken online and over the phone.We accept all major credit and debit cards, as well as payments via PayPal.Popular CategoriesBirthday BannersWedding BannersWelcome Home BannersPersonalised PostersGood Luck BannersSpecial OccasionsChristeningsRetirementBaby Shower & New BabyGraduation & ExamsFuneralsHelp & SupportContact UsDelivery InformationReturns & RefundsPrivacy PolicyTerms & ConditionsSite NavigationHomeCustomer ReviewsSocial Media PolicyYour BasketSite MapBanner InformationFrequently Asked QuestionsBanner SizesDelivery TimescalesPricing InformationPhoto EnquiryYour AccountNew AccountSign InWish ListView Basket
Copyright © 2020 HTD Graphics Ltd, trading as Bannerama. All rights reserved. Registered in England & Wales 06091854.Indoor & outdoor personalised banners & postersMost orders created & dispatched within 48 hours!              Call us on01473 832851£0.00 0Full ShopBirthday BannersMen's BirthdayWomen's Birthday18th & 21st BirthdayChildren's BirthdayTeenage BirthdayFootball BirthdaysSport Themed BannersUpright / Door BannersThis Is Your LifeWedding BannersWeddingsEngagementHen PartyWedding AnniversaryProposalMore BannersCongratulationsNaming Ceremony BannersFuneral / Memorial BannersRetirementSchool BannersGraduation BannersBaby Shower / New BabyPet BannersChristmas & New YearCOVID-19Special OccasionsGood Luck BannersChristening BannersWelcome Home BannersMilitary BannersPostersThis is Your LifeBirthdayAnniversaryGood LuckWeddingWelcome Home
